Ahmed Al-hob

CONTACT E-mail: ahmedalhob112@gmail.com

Phone: +966541209221

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I am a digital marketing professional with more than 6 years experience in digital marketing, e-commerce, Social media, Content creation and Copy-writing with ability to effectively develop, manage and control relationships between the company and its target audience, enjoying challenging briefs & able to work to an excellent standards under considerable pressure

EDUCATION Applied N

Applied Marketing Diploma April 2016 — November 2016

Regional IT Institute, Cairo, Egypt

Faculty Of Commerce and Business September 2009 — May 2013 Administration, English Section

Al-Azhar University in Cairo

WORK EXPERIENCE Nobles, KSA

Dec. 2018 — Sep. 2019

Digital Marketing Manager

The overall scope of my position was to plan and execute the company's all digital marketing and E-commerce activities including but not limited to:

Developing and executing the digital marketing strategies, including social media, Influencers marketing, online advertising, community management, mobile marketing programs, SEO, SEM & Display advertising to achieve Marketing & Business objectives Preparing annual budget for the digital marketing, monitoring competitors strategies and industry trends

Identifying consumer insights & purchase behavior to develop communication strategy across owned & earned digital platforms

End to end management of Digital & Social media campaigns – creative, innovations and media for the New Product Launches and new store openings to drive awareness and generate demand

Leading the internal and agency teams to deliver exceptional performance Analyzing the performance of digital channels and campaigns and identify and execute optimizations to maximize effectiveness

Reporting digital marketing activities, results and budget to CEO

Qasr Alawani, KSA

Dec. 2016 — Dec. 2018

Senior Digital Marketing Executive

Planning, implementing, tracking and optimizing digital marketing campaigns across all digital channels including SEO/SEM, and email marketing campaigns in order to increase sales and brand awareness

Developing engaging, creative, content for regularly Social media posts, and paid ads, which enlighten more than 1M followers and promote brand-focused messages across different platforms including Instagram, Snapchat, Facebook and twitter

Building and maintaining online and social media presence in collaboration with internal team and external vendors Implementing and optimizing paid campaigns across different digital and social media channels

Managing influencers campaigns

Leading digital marketing team members, including designers, photographers and content creators, by overseeing their work and offering guidance and direction

Reporting digital marketing activities, results and budget to senior management

Ahmed Al-hoh

Digital Marketing Executive

Planning and executing digital marketing campaigns, including SEO/SEM,paid ads campaigns, and email marketing campaigns

Building and maintaining company's online presence in collaboration with other team members

Creating content for digital channels and developing creative ideas for branding/messaging

Analyzing and monitoring online campaigns and social media Defining trends and insights, and optimize spend and performance based on the insights Delegating day-to-day tasks to the Marketing Manager Supporting the marketing manager and other colleagues

Walfarm Pharmaceuticals, Egypt

August 2013 — March 2015

Marketing Specialist

Coordinating and executing marketing plans & Branding campaigns across the entire network

Liaising and networking with a range of stakeholders including customers, colleagues, suppliers and partner organizations

Managing the production of marketing materials, including leaflets, posters, flyers and brochures Arranging the effective distribution of marketing materials

Organizing and attending events such as conferences and exhibitions Writing and proofreading marketing copy for both online and printed campaigns

Liaising with designers and printers and organizing photo shoots Planning and executing online, web, social media email marketing campaigns

Monitoring market trends, research consumer markets and competitors' activities to identify opportunities and key issues

CERTIFICATES

E-Commerce Certified - e-marketing institute Google Ads Search Certified - Google Academy Google Ads Display Certified - Google Academy Google Analytics Certified - Google Academy E-Commerce Certified - e-marketing institute Social Media Management Certified- Hootsuite Snap Chat Ads Certified - Snapchat

LANGUAGES

Arabic & English

REFERENCES

References available upon request.

Ahmed Al-hob

2